See, that's really what force is based in many times.
Fear and ego.
Is this decision I'm making to either move or not move,
is this based in ego or fear?
That's a great way to identify force.
Because ultimately, my reasoning for like,
I'm going to show them, was both ego and fear.
Ego, that who the hell they think they are playing in my face.
Like that one time Whitney was singing
That's What Friends Are For with Luther Vandross.
And he had let her know,
Oh, I'm looser.
Yeah, he had to let her know.
But it was also fear that these people think
they're going to get away with playing in my face.
Like, what are you, who cares?
What are you afraid of?
What are you proving?
Who are these people?
That's force.
And that's when I realized what I need to do
is I need to bring an Amanda We Trust to the people
and I need to figure out how to do it.
But that has been a project that has come through in flow.
So why am I stepping out of that?
I think there's a tiếp because there's a hard or agile thing.
There are definitely things that could help move to life and build,
with the past or leadership.
Mm-hm.
What's your career I see in your view,
and build the opportunity,
and build the purpose
and build thesecurity problem
with good support
and build everything.